### **PROFILE**

Two years ago, I decided to pursue my passion in the field of AI. I joined a Master's program while maintaining a full-time job. The AI field unleashes my creativity and allows me to build fun and meaningful projects. I enjoy every moment of being in this field.

### RESEARCH PROJECTS

Vertex2Image - Construct Human Figure Based On A Monocular Video Published At ACM IUI 2023 Conference

**3D Pose Estimation From Multi-View 2D Joints' Locations** Target At ICCV 2023 Conference

### WORKING EXPERIENCES

# HanMa Cemetery Service LLC, Harbin, China Remote Contractor

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

The company provides cemetery services for Muslim communities in China. The business part I involved in is to use the ArcGIS interface to provide tomb locations based on name searches.

- use a self-supervised model to generate pseudo labels in their raw image dataset for downstream applications
- design a deep learning model to recognize text information in the images and reduced 76% of the workload for employees
- create an internal tool to increase employees' productivity. The average input time of an employee is reduced from 90 seconds per image to 30 seconds per image

### Sci-Bots LLC, San Francisco, CA Founder

Jan 2021 - Jun 2022

Sci-Bots is a non-profit organization that teaches kids between 6 and 10 years old to learn about micro-controller, programming, and robotics in a fun way. We collaborate with DJI and MG Space to design the curriculum. Our website: <a href="https://www.sci-bots.org">www.sci-bots.org</a>

- serve as the main curriculum designer and developed 3 classes
- train lecturers for new class materials every week
- supervise class flow and progress

# CP Capital Group Inc., Dixon, CA Assistant Manager

May 2017 - Jan 2023

The company owns several hotel businesses in the Bay Area and operates tourism business for regular travel groups, student groups, and delegation groups.

- oversee daily operations
- establish and maintain relationships with vendors and clients
- prepare monthly and yearly data dashboard

### **EDUCATION**

Master of Science in Computer Science Graduated on Dec 2022

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, California

Master of Business Administration Graduated on Jun 2019

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, California



## ZACH Z. WANG

Software Engineer

Phone:

(415) 272 - 6740

E-Mail:

2010zihao@gmail.com

GitHub:

zachs-playground.github.io

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zach-wang-784b1a90/

Primary Languages:

C++, C#, Python, CUDA

Familiar Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript

Focus Areas:

Computer Vision,
Virtual Reality,
Deep Learning,
Reinforcement Learning,
Simulation